

#### **SUMMARY**

I have been a basketball player and team captain in the regional league for 13 years, and I have also been a 5-year E-Level Basketball Coach. For this reason, being in the team concept has helped me a lot in terms of both human management and teamwork and empathy. I work as a full-stack software developer in the IT industry.

#### **CONTACT INFO**

# PHONE:

0506-221-18-03

#### LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/atbostan

# **EMAIL:**

a.tarikbostan@gmail.com

#### MEDIUM:

https://medium.com/@atbostan.developer

# AHMET TARIK BOSTAN SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Software Engineer Softtech

2021- Ongoing

I carry out the development and maintenance of banking and banking applications. In addition, I am involved in the transition process of the projects of the team I am affiliated with within the scope of technology transformation. The technologies I use in this context are mainly .Net , Java , Javascript and Cobol.

# Software Engineer Magiclik Digital Solutions

2021

I took part in the application development team using .Net and .Net Core technologies. I supported the CMS projects of many institutions from banking to private institutions.

# Software Engineer Business Intelligence Bridge

2020-202

I develop Web-based projects using Angular on the Front-End side, .NET and .NET Core on the Back-End, and PostgreSql and MySql on the Database. I took part in all end-to-end processes from the deployment of these projects to the Docker environment.

#### Cashier-Accounting

Inditex-Zara

2019-2020

I worked in the in-store buying and selling department.

#### E Level Basketball Coach

# Clubs Affiliated to Turkish Basketball Federation , ANKARA

2012-2019

I have worked with athletes of all ages and coached and guided them to become a good individual and then a good athlete both in their professional and private lives.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Master- Software Engineering

2020-2022

Hacettepe University

#### **Bachelor-Statistic**

2015-2019

Ankara University

# **EXAMINATION INFO**

YDS - Score:80

08.09.2019

YÖKDİL – Score:87

01.09.2018

# COMPETENCIES

# **Programming Languages**

- \*C#
- \*Html
- \*JavaScript
- \*Css, Scss
- \*TypeScript
- \*COBOL

#### **Frontend Libraries**

- \*Angular Material
- \*PrimeNG
- \*Ngx Bootstrap
- \*Boostrap 4
- \*React.js
- \*Redux

#### **Framework**

- \*Angular
- \*ASP.NET
- \*ASP.NET CORE
- \*ASP.NET Web Forms

#### **ORM Tools**

\*EntityFramework

#### **Database**

- \*PostgreSql
- \*MySal
- \*DB2
- \*Firebase

#### **Web Application Framework**

- \*Asp.Net BoilerPlate
- \*Asp.Net BoilerPlate Zero

# **Backend Techs.**

- \*Hanafire
- \*FastReport
- \*Autofac
- \*Fluent Validation
- \*Asp.Net Identity

# **PROJECTS**

#### Softtech

Mission: Software Engineer

Job Desc.: Developing and maintaining all businesses connected to işbank's deposit team and starting to develop them in all channels (branch, işCep, etc.) within the scope of technology transformation.

#### **Magiclick Digital Solutions**

Project Name: Medipol Hospitals ve Medipol University Cms Project

Mission: Software Engineer

**Job Desc.:** Development and maintenance of content application made with Asp.Net Web forms technology using Microservice Architecture

# Business Intelligence Bridge

**Project Name:** NACORAC (National Center for Coordination and Joint Risk Analysis)

Mission: Software Engineer

**Job Desc:** Database design with PostgreSql using Microservice Architecture, writing APIs with ASP.NET Core on the back-end, user interface designs with Angular 8+ on the front-end.

Project Name: Online Exam System

Mission: Software Engineer

**Job Desc:** It has been developed for primary, secondary and high school students using Angular 8+ on the Front-End side, .Net Core on the Back-End side, PostgreSql as the database, and Big Blue Button, a video conferencing technology to provide a secure environment.

**Project Name:** Smart Agenda Student Homework Responsibility Tracking System

Mission: Software Engineer

**Job Desc:** It has been developed by using Angular 8+ on the Front-End side and .Net Core on the Back-End side and PostgreSql as the database, as an application where students can follow their homework and various other responsibilities as well as their activities. It is currently used as a demo by **Norman Schools.** 

Project Name: Easy Memorization

Mission: Software Engineer

Job Desc: By using Angular 8+ on the Front-End side and .Net Core on the Back-End side and PostgreSql as the database, the system determines the words that students need to memorize on a daily basis, by uploading the concepts that students want to memorize, both textual and pictures and pdfs, using a specific algorithm. A memorization assistant application that presents these words to students has been developed. It is currently used as a demo by Norman Schools.

Project Name: Digital Archive File and Folder Sharing System

Mission: Software Engineer

**Job Desc:** File and folder sharing system has been developed using Angular 11 on the Front-End side and .Net Core on the Back-End side and PostgreSql as the database. Hadoop is used as the file storage system.